A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants E-G FA732C FA732C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - E to G
  - Florida International University (10251150), 2002 July 01-2004 June 30 (Reel 9084)
    For the Cuban Research Institute to conduct academic exchanges between Cuban and Cuban Americans and host the 5th Conference on Cuban and Cuban-American Studies
  - Florida Justice Institute, Inc. (08500225), 1985 January 22-1987 January 21 (Reel 4639;4640)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE NATIONAL INTEREST ON LAWYER TRUST ACCOUNT CLEARINGHOUSE
    United States; Florida Justice Institute, Inc.
  - Florida Lutheran Council on Social Ministry, Inc. (08150686), 1981 July 01-1981 November 30 (Reel 3739)
    TO ENABLE THE COUNCIL'S MIAMI DIVISION TO DEVELOP A SERVICE PROGRAM FOR CUBANS/HAITIANS
    Florida Lutheran Council on Social Ministry, Inc.
  - Florida Lutheran Council on Social Ministry, Inc. (08250414), 1982 January 01-1982 December 31 (Reel 3373)
    SUPPORT TO ENABLE THE COUNCIL TO CONTINUE TO DEVELOP A SERVICE PROGRAM FOR CUBANS AND HAITIANS IN THE MIAMI-DADE COUNTY AREA
    Biggers, Patricia
    Miami (Fla.); Florida Lutheran Council on Social Ministry, Inc.
  - Florida Memorial College, Inc. (06700394), 1967 July 19-1968 July 18 (Reel 1862)
    Florida Memorial College, Inc.
  - Florida Memorial College, Inc. (06700499), 1967 August 24-1968 August 23 (Reel 1865)
  - Florida Memorial College, Inc. (06800285), 1968 April 22-1969 June 21 (Reel 2028)
    $1,586.00;$1,586.00
  - Florida Memorial College, Inc. (07850392), 1978 January 15-1979 January 14 (Reel 2196)
    TO DEVELOP PLANS AND PROCEDURES FOR ESTABLISHING LONG RANGE PLANNING AND MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEMS
    Miami (Fla.); Florida Memorial College, Inc.
  - Florida Memorial College, Inc. (08150182), 1980 December 15-1981 December 14 (Reel 2668)
    SUPPORT STUDY OF FEASIBILITY OF DEVELOPING AN FHA HOUSING PROJECT ON THE COLLEGE'S OLD CAMPUS
  - Florida Normal and Industrial Memorial College (05600416), 1956 June 29-1966 June 28 (Reel 0303)
    Florida Normal and Industrial Memorial College
  - Florida Presbyterian College (06600119), 1966 July 01-1970 June 30 (Reel 1454)
    PROGRAM OF INDEPENDENT STUDY FOR SELECTED STUDENTS
    Florida Presbyterian College
  - Florida Presbyterian College (06800416), 1968 June 01-1972 May 31 (Reel 1895)
  - Florida Southern College (05600417), 1956 June 29-1966 June 28 (Reel 0303)
    $368,000.00;$368,000.00
    Florida Southern College
  - Florida State Legislature (07700494), 1977 July 01-1978 August 31 (Reel 2762)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A STUDY TO ASSESS IMPACT AND EFFECTIVENESS OF 1973 REFORMS IN EDUCATION FINANCE AND GOVERNANCE
    $62,341.00;$53,469.50
    Florida; Florida State Legislature
  - Florida State University (06300069), 1962 December 17-1968 September 16 (Reel 2579)
    $250,000.00;$240,500.92
    Florida State University
  - Florida State University (06400233), 1964 April 14-1969 April 13 (Reel 2128)
    SPECIAL STUDIES AND CONSULTATIVE SERVICES IN THE CAPE KENNEDY AREA
  - Florida State University (06600403), 1966 August 03-1967 November 02 (Reel 1260;5977)
    ESTABLISHMENT OF A NATIONAL SCIENCE LYCEE IN ANKARA
    $95,324.00;$95,324.00
    Sharpe, Richard S.
    Turkey; Florida State University
  - Florida State University (06700586), 1967 October 20-1973 February 28 (Reel 1105)
    ESTABLISHMENT OF A SOUTH-EASTERN RESEARCH CENTER IN CORRECTIONS AND CRIMINOLOGY
    Milbourn, Joan C.
  - Florida State University (06900451), 1969 May 29-1970 May 28 (Reel 1944)
    FACULTY RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN ECONOMICS, POLITICAL SCIENCE AND SOCIOLOGY, 1969-1970
    $13,800.00;$13,754.86
  - Florida State University (07450298), 1974 January 01-1974 September 30 (Reel 1337)
    SUPPORT FOR A NATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON POLICY ISSUES IN POSTSECONDARY EDUCATION
    $14,700.00;$14,700.00
    United States; Florida State University
  - Florida State University (07500584), 1975 September 15-1978 September 14 (Reel 2839)
    DETERMINING THE ACTUAL AIMS OF RUSSIA IN ASIA
    Gaer, Felice D.
    Soviet Union; Florida State University
  - Florida State University (07650058), 1975 October 15-1976 December 31 (Reel 1401)
    EXPENSES TO ENABLE SCHOLARS FROM DEVELOPING WORLD TO PARTICIPATE IN RELATION BETWEEN URBAN AND RURAL DEVELOPMENT
    $7,690.00;$7,361.64
    Global; Florida State University
  - Florida State University (07650272), 1976 April 21-1976 June 20 (Reel 2361)
    TRAVEL AND PER DIEM COSTS FOR SIX STUDENTS TO ATTEND THE POPULATION ASSOC. OF AMERICA MEETING IN MONTREAL, 4/29 TO 5/1/76
    $2,261.00;$2,261.00
    Horn, Majorie C.
    Indonesia; Thailand; Florida State University
  - Florida State University (07750176), 1977 January 01-1979 December 31 (Reel 2538)
    SUPPORT OF THE CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF POPULATION
    Population [POP];Asia & The Pacific [ASIA]
    Geithner, Peter F.;Harkavy, Oscar
  - Florida State University (08050661), 1981 January 01-1981 December 31 (Reel 3367)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR PUBLICATION OF "BALANCE OF INTRIGUE: INTERNA- TIONAL RIVALRY IN KOREA AND MANCHURIA 1884 1899" BY PROF. LENSEN
    Soviet Union; North Asia; Florida State University
  - Florida State University (08100294), 1981 March 01-1982 July 31 (Reel 4994)
    RESEARCH ON "INHIBIN," A GONADAL INHIBITOR OF REPRODUCTIVE FUNCTION
    $147,889.00;$147,889.00
  - Florida State University (08201072), 1982 September 01-1987 February 28 (Reel 5486)
    RESEARCH ON GONADOTROPIN RELEASING HORMONE AND ITS ANALOGS
    Population Program
    $336,734.00;$336,707.72
  - Florida State University (08400122), 1984 January 01-1985 November 30 (Reel 6046)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF ARTICULATION AND TRANSFER POLICIES IN EIGHT STATES
    $70,000.00;$65,849.84
  - Florida State University (08900909), 1989 August 01-1997 December 31 (Reel 7896)
    CONTINUED SUPPORT FOR PROGRAM ACTIVITIES OF THE FLORIDA MINORITY TEACHER CONSORTIUM
    $3,872,000.00;$3,872,000.00
    United States; Florida; Florida State University
  - Florida State University (08950412), 1988 December 01-1990 July 30 (Reel 6229)
    TO CONVENE A CONSORTIUM OF INSTITUTIONS PARTICIPATING IN THE FOUNDATION'S MINORITY TEACHER EDUCATION PROGRAM IN FLORIDA AND TO HELP DEVELOP PROPOSALS
    Florida; Florida State University
  - Florida Symphony Society, Inc. (06600283), 1966 July 01-1976 June 30 (Reel 2979;2980;4342)
    Florida Symphony Society, Inc.
  - Florida West Coast Educational Television, Inc. (05900382), 1959 July 08-1962 August 03 (Reel 0177)
    EXPERIMENTAL PROJECT IN EDUCATIONAL TELEVISION
    $155,500.00;$155,500.00
    Florida West Coast Educational Television, Inc.
  - Florida West Coast Educational Television, Inc. (06000065), 1960 April 05-1961 April 03 (Reel 0209)
    IMPROVEMENT OF TEACHING IN CONNECTION WITH NATIONAL PROGRAM IN USE OF TELEVISION IN PUBLIC SCHOOLS
    $19,760.00;$19,760.00
  - Florida West Coast Educational Television, Inc. (06600076), 1965 December 14-1977 January 03 (Reel 1456)
    $133,787.00;$133,787.00
  - Florida West Coast Educational Television, Inc. (06700476), 1967 August 09-1977 August 08 (Reel 3929;5473)
    $63,785.00;$63,785.00
  - Florida West Coast Educational Television, Inc. (06800534), 1968 June 10-1978 June 09 (Reel 5657)
  - Flowers With Care (08250411), 1982 February 01-1983 January 31 (Reel 3373)
    TO DEVELOP A FIRM BASE OF FINANCIAL SUPPORT IN ORDER TO EXPAND AND INSTITUTIONALIZE FLOWERS WITH CARE'S PROGRAM
    Carol, Joy
    New York (State); Flowers With Care
  - Flynn Theatre for the Performing Arts, Ltd. (10000820), 2000 April 01-2005 June 30 (Reel 9109)
    SUPPORT TO ADVANCE EXEMPLARY ARTISTIC INITIATIVES BY INCREASING PERMANENT CAPITAL, EXPANDING THE INDIVIDUAL DONOR BASE, AND ENHANCING BOARD LEADERSHIP
    $1,250,000.00;$1,250,000.00
    United States; Arts -- United States -- Endowments; Flynn Theatre for the Performing Arts, Ltd.
  - Focus (Russia) (10150296), 2001 January 01-2003 December 31 (Reel 9279)
    Support to establish the professions of fundraiser and development officer in Russia and to aid these individuals with training, technical assistance, and networking
    $148,000.00;$148,000.00
    Kedzie, Christopher R.
    Russia; Nonprofit organizations--Management--Russia (Federation); Fund raising -- Russia (Federation); Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations -- Russia (Federation); Management--Training of--Russia (Federation); Focus (Russia)
  - Focus HOPE (07700435), 1977 June 01-1981 June 30 (Reel 2505)
    SUPPORT OF SCHOOL DESEGREGATION ACTIVITIES IN METROPOLITAN DETROIT
    Hertz, Willard J.;Lynch, Barbara D.;Meade, Edward J.
    Detroit (Mich.); Focus HOPE
  - Focus HOPE (08400120), 1984 February 01-1985 January 31 (Reel 5113)
    ADMINISTRATIVE AND SUPPORT COSTS
    Arrick, Ellen
    Michigan; Focus HOPE
  - Focus HOPE (10001605), 2000 August 01-2001 December 31 (Reel 8779)
    SUPPORT TO DEVELOP ADMINISTRATIVE AND MANAGEMENT PROCEDURES FOR A STUDENT LOAN FUND ESTABLISHED TO PROVIDE TUITION ASSISTANCE TO FOCUS: HOPE'S TRAINING AND EDUCATION PROGRAM PARTICIPANTS
    Detroit (Mich.); Student Loans--United States; Focus HOPE
  - Focus on the Global South (10001225), 2000 June 01-2005 October 31 (Reel 9162)
    SUPPORT FOR POLICY-ORIENTED RESEARCH, CONFERENCES, TRAINING WORKSHOPS, AND PRODUCTION OF ECONOMIC LITERACY MATERIALS ON ALTERNATIVE APPROACHES IN ECONOMIC GLOBALIZATION
    PSJ - Office of the Vice President;Human Rights;Governance and Civil Society
    Montes, Manuel F.;Jordan, Lisa
    SouthEast Asia; Global; Development economics -- Research; International trade; International finance--Research; Focus on the Global South
  - Focus on the Global South (10450147), 2003 November 15-2004 November 14 (Reel 9206)
    To strengthen participation of marginalized communities in the World Social Forum process
    $0.00;$0.00
    Raman, Sushma
    India; Focus on the Global South
  - Focus Society for Developmental Research and Communication (08550675), 1985 May 16-1985 November 15 (Reel 5236)
    PRODUCTION OF PRINTS OF THE DOCUMENTARY FILM "SHANTI DEVI - AN ARTIST IN MADHUBANI" FOR DISSEMINATION AND TRAINING PURPOSES (INDIA)
    Bennett, Lynn
    India; Focus Society for Developmental Research and Communication
  - Folger Shakespeare Memorial Library (05500031), 1954 (Reel 0190)
    PRELIMINARY EXPLORATION OF PHOTODUPLICATION FOR EXTENSION OF LIBRARY SERVICES
    $25,000.00;$11,588.87
    Folger Shakespeare Memorial Library
  - Folger Shakespeare Memorial Library (06400174), 1964 February 07-1965 February 06 (Reel 0948)
    ACTIVITIES OF THE NATIONAL SHAKESPEARE ANNIVERSARY COMMITTEE
    $250,000.00;$170,950.32
  - Folklore Society of South Indian Languages (09301431), 1994 February 17-2003 December 28 (Reel 9237)
    SUPPORT FOR STRENGTHENING FOLKLORE NETWORKING AND DISSEMINATION IN SOUTH ASIA
    $230,000.00;$230,000.00
    India; Folklore Society of South Indian Languages
  - Folkworks, Inc. (08550990), 1985 July 01-1985 December 31 (Reel 5305)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT TO ESTABLISH ITS OPERATIONS AND ENHANCE ITS CAPACITY TO PLAN AND PRODUCE SPECIAL EVENTS FOR NONPROFIT ORGANIZATIONS
    New York (N.Y.); Folkworks, Inc.
  - Folkworks, Inc. (08750561), 1987 January 01-1987 June 30 (Reel 5756)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE SPECIAL EVENTS PRODUCTION TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE PROGRAM (SEPTA)
  - Fomento Cultural Y Educativo, A.C. (07550351), 1975 April 01-1975 June 30 (Reel 2890;3206)
    EVALUATION MEETING OF THE TRAINING COURSE FOR EDUCATIONAL EXPERIMENTATION COORDINATORS
    $740.00;$740.00
    Myers, Robert G.;Seay, George Liston
    Fomento Cultural Y Educativo, A.C.
  - Fomento Cultural Y Educativo, A.C. (07850313), 1978 January 01-1978 December 31 (Reel 1284;4716)
    RESEARCH PROJECT ON "PEASANT WOMEN BETWEEN RURAL UNDERDEVELOPMENT AND COUNTRY INDUSTRIALIZATION: THEIR POTENTIAL AND LIMITATIONS...
    $4,541.00;$4,541.00
    Cleaves, Peter S.;Friedman, Jonathan A.;Hertford, Reed
    Mexico; Fomento Cultural Y Educativo, A.C.
  - Fomento Cultural Y Educativo, A.C. (08250814), 1982 March 01-1983 February 28 (Reel 3639;5314)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE HEALTH EDUCATION PROJECT IN MECAYAPAN-CHINAMECA, VERACRUZ, MEXICO
    $13,970.00;$13,335.00
  - Fomento Cultural Y Educativo, A.C. (08600221), 1986 January 01-1986 December 31 (Reel 5522;5736)
    SUPPORT POST-EARTHQUAKE RECONSTRUCTION IN LOW-INCOME NEIGHBORHOODS IN MEXICO CITY
    $95,000.00;$94,522.60
  - Fondation Charles Leopold Mayer Pour le Progres de l'Homme (10251970), 2002 September 02-2004 September 01 (Reel 9196)
    For the Intercultural Library Program to encourage dialogue between different cultures through the written word
    Global; Fondation Charles Leopold Mayer Pour le Progres de l'Homme
  - Fondation Du Present (10001049), 2000 April 01-2002 March 31 (Reel 8884)
    SUPPORT TO FACILITATE, MAINTAIN, AND PROMOTE NEW INTERNET LISTSERVES FOR HIV-RELATED ISSUES IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES
    Global; AIDS (Disease) -- Information services -- Developing Countries; Fondation Du Present
  - Fondation Pour Le Centre Europeen Feminin De Recherche Sur L'Evolution De La Societe (07900438), 1979 June 01-1981 May 31 (Reel 2513)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE CEFRES ASSOCIATION'S ACTIVITIES
    Education & Culture Program [EC];European and International Affairs
    Chamberlain, Mariam;Ruof, Peter;Saario, Terry
    Europe; Fondation Pour Le Centre Europeen Feminin De Recherche Sur L'Evolution De La Societe
  - Fondation Pour Une Entraide Intellectuelle Europeenne (07800125), 1978 January 01-1980 December 31 (Reel 3542)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR PROGRAM INVOLVING INTELLECTUALS AND ARTISTS INEASTERN EUROPE
    European and International Affairs;Education & Culture Program [EC];Education and Public Policy
    Europe, Eastern; Fondation Pour Une Entraide Intellectuelle Europeenne
  - Fondation Pour Une Entraide Intellectuelle Europeenne (08100352), 1981 January 01-1983 December 31 (Reel 4219)
    PROVISION OF A RESERVE FUND AND GENERAL SUPPORT FOR PROGRAM INVOLVING INTELLECTUALS AND ARTISTS IN EASTERN EUROPE
  - Fondation Pour Une Entraide Intellectuelle Europeenne (08250378), 1982 January 15-1983 June 30 (Reel 3704)
    EMERGENCY ASSISTANCE TO POLISH INTELLECTUALS IN WESTERN EUROPE
    Poland; Fondation Pour Une Entraide Intellectuelle Europeenne
  - Fondation Pour Une Entraide Intellectuelle Europeenne (08400228), 1984 January 01-1991 December 31 (Reel 6373)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR TRAVEL AND STUDY AND OTHER EXCHANGE PROGRAMS FOR INTELLECTUALS AND ARTISTS IN EASTERN EUROPE
    $1,021,998.00;$1,021,998.00
  - Fondation Pour Une Entraide Intellectuelle Europeenne (08751138), 1987 October 01-1988 September 30 (Reel 5291)
    SUPPORT FOR A MAJOR FUNDRAISING EFFORT IN THE UNITED STATES AND EUROPE
    Picken, Margo
  - Fondation Tunisienne Pour Le Developpement Communautaire (09150448), 1991 January 01-1992 March 31 (Reel 6081)
    SUPPORT TO STRENGTHEN FTDC'S ORGANIZATIONAL CAPABILITIES IN FUND-RAISING
    Tunisia; Fondation Tunisienne Pour Le Developpement Communautaire
  - Fondation Tunisienne Pour Le Developpement Communautaire (09200648), 1992 April 01-1994 December 31 (Reel 7119;8699)
    SUPPORT FOR THE STRENGTHENING OF THE FOUNDATION'S FUND-RAISING CAPABILITIES
    $116,000.00;$116,000.00
  - Fondation Youssou Ndour (10251973), 2002 September 15-2003 September 14 (Reel 9207)
    To develop and implement a training program in business development and cultural entrepreneurship skills for talented young musicians from West Africa
    Human Development and Reproductive Health;Media Arts and Culture
    Floyd, Virginia Davis;Pwono, Damien M.
    Africa, West; Fondation Youssou Ndour
  - Fondo Pro Naturaleza (09600516), 1996 February 01-1997 October 30 (Reel 7730)
    TIE-OFF SUPPORT FOR AN EDUCATION AND RESEARCH PROGRAM ON ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT IN THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
    Dominican Republic; Fondo Pro Naturaleza
  - Fontbonne College (05600631), 1956 June 29-1966 June 28 (Reel 0315)
    $158,500.00;$158,500.00
    Fontbonne College
  - Food and Agricultural Research Management Ltd (09450654), 1994 March 01-1995 February 28 (Reel 6729;7247)
    PARTIAL FUNDING FOR A WORKSHOP ON PARTICIPATORY FOREST MANAGEMENT IN ETHIOPIA
    $16,495.00;$16,495.00
    Ethiopia; Food and Agricultural Research Management Ltd
  - Food and Agricultural Research Management Ltd (09550352), 1994 December 01-1995 November 30 (Reel 7137)
    STUDY TOUR TO INDIA FOR SENIOR AFRICAN FORESTERS
    $71,600.00;$71,600.00
    Africa, East; Africa, Southern; Food and Agricultural Research Management Ltd
  - Food And Agriculture Organization (07350858), 1973 August 22-1974 August 21 (Reel 1774;4277;4612)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF THE USE OF AGRICULTURAL TAXES AND SUBSIDIES IN CHILE
    Chile; Food And Agriculture Organization
  - Food And Agriculture Organization of The United Nations (05100024), 1951 (Reel 0487)
    SEND OBSERVERS FROM NON-GOVERNMENTAL ORGANIZATIONS TO FAO CONFERENCES IN ROME
    Food And Agriculture Organization of The United Nations
  - Food And Agriculture Organization of The United Nations (05900291), 1959 June 16-1960 June 15 (Reel 0701)
    SECOND LATIN AMERICAN SEMINAR ON LAND PROBLEMS
    $10,000.00;$6,279.28
  - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (08350432), 1983 April 01-1984 September 30 (Reel 5063;7001)
    SUPPORT FOR WOMEN'S ASSOCIATIONS ON RESETTLEMENT SITES
    $48,200.00;$48,200.00
    Ethiopia; Food And Agriculture Organization of The United Nations
  - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (08550872), 1985 June 01-1986 May 31 (Reel 5857)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF AGRICULTURAL DELIVERY SYSTEMS TO SMALL FARMERS IN WEST AFRICA
    $45,000.00;$44,253.41
    Senegal; Burkina Faso; Food And Agriculture Organization of The United Nations
  - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (08600276), 1986 February 01-1991 March 31 (Reel 5935)
    SUPPORT TO ENHANCE AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTION EFFORTS BY WOMEN IN ETHIOPIA
    $176,000.00;$176,000.00
  - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (09900961), 1999 April 01-2004 March 31 (Reel 9161)
    SUPPORT FOR PRODUCTION OF BOOK SYNTHESIZING WORLDWIDE EXPERIENCE IN THE DEVOLUTION OF IRRIGATION MANAGEMENT
    India, Nepal and Sri Lanka (New Delhi);Assets - Office of the Vice President
    Belbase, Narayan;Coward, E. Walter
    Global; Irrigation--Management--Global; Food And Agriculture Organization of The United Nations
  - Food Research and Action Center, Incorporated (08200967), 1982 September 01-1996 December 31 (Reel 7099)
    TRANSITIONAL SUPPORT GRANTS FOR ORGANIZATIONS WHICH PROVIDE BACK-UP SUPPORT TO LOCAL LEGAL SERVICES OFFICES
    $1,230,000.00;$1,230,000.00
    United States; Hunger -- United States; Children -- Health and hygiene -- United States; Public welfare--United States; Food Research and Action Center, Incorporated
  - Food Research and Action Center, Incorporated (08251114), 1982 September 01-1983 August 31 (Reel 4679)
    SPECIAL PROJECT TO MONITOR THE WIC PROGRAM AT THE NATIONAL LEVEL AND PROVIDE INFORMATION TO COMMUNITIES
    United States; Food Research and Action Center, Incorporated
  - Food Research and Action Center, Incorporated (08400224), 1984 February 01-1988 December 31 (Reel 5666)
    SUPPORT FOR FRAC'S PUBLIC POLICY WORK IN MATERNAL AND CHILD HEALTH AND NUTRITION
    $467,000.00;$467,000.00
  - Food Research and Action Center, Incorporated (08550528), 1985 May 01-1986 April 30 (Reel 5249)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF FOOD ASSISTANCE PROGRAMS FOR THE RURAL POOR
  - Food Research and Action Center, Incorporated (08850742), 1988 June 01-1989 February 28 (Reel 5701)
    SUPPORT FOR RURAL COMPONENT OF COMMUNITY HUNGER SURVEY PROJECT
  - Food, Nutrition + Health, Inc. (07000080), 1969 December 01-1971 April 30 (Reel 1665)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON "FOOD, NUTRITION AND HEALTH" TO BE HELD AT THE WHITE HOUSE DECEMBER 2-4, 1969
    $300,000.00;$226,252.50
    Sviridoff, Mitchell
    Food, Nutrition + Health, Inc.
  - For Responsive Media:citizens Communications Center (07200159), 1972 March 28-1981 February 28 (Reel 2481;2482;2783)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR THE CENTER'S ACTIVITIES IN PUBLIC INTEREST LAW IN THE FIELD OF COMMUNICATIONS
    National Affairs [NA];Office of Communications (pre 1979);Education and Public Policy
    $2,040,000.00;$2,040,000.00
    Davis, David M.;Jaffe, Sanford M.
    United States; For Responsive Media:citizens Communications Center
  - For Responsive Media:citizens Communications Center (07950476), 1979 April 01-1979 June 30 (Reel 2391)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE SEVENTH ANNUAL TELECOMMUNICATIONS POLICY RESEARCH CONFERENCE, HELD APRIL 29 THROUGH MAY 1, 1979
    $10,000.00;$7,618.71
    For Responsive Media:citizens Communications Center
  - For the Record (09250457), 1992 February 01-1993 February 01 (Reel 7117)
    TRANSLATION, PUBLICATION AND DISSEMINATION OF ISRAELI PRESS MATERIAL THAT ADDRESSES ISSUES RELATING TO THE ARAB ISRAELI CONFLICT
    Africa & The Middle East [AME];International Affairs Program [IA]
    Back, Aaron I.;Forman, Shepard
    Middle East; For the Record
  - Fordham University (05600684), 1956 June 29-1966 June 28 (Reel 0319)
    $1,424,000.00;$1,424,000.00
    Fordham University
  - Fordham University (05601049), 1956 June 29-1957 June 28 (Reel 0337)
    $883,500.00;$883,500.00
  - Fordham University (05700228), 1957 May 16-1958 May 15 (Reel 0065)
    CASE-METHOD SEMINAR AT HARVARD BUSINESS SCHOOL
  - Fordham University (06400435), 1964 August 17-1966 February 16 (Reel 2012;2013)
    CONFERENCE ON PHILOSOPHIC AND SCIENTIFIC PROBLEMS ARISING FROM THE HYPOTHESIS OF CONVERGENT EVOLUTION
    $25,000.00;$15,281.31
  - Fordham University (06700227), 1967 April 25-1968 April 24 (Reel 1878)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF AN INTERNSHIP PROGRAM /UNDERGRADUATE AND GRADUATE/ IN THE NEW YORK STATE CONSTITUTIONAL CONVENTION
    $40,000.00;$39,351.05
  - Fordham University (08000596), 1980 June 01-1982 May 01 (Reel 3559)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT TO FORDHAM UNIVERSITY'S HISPANIC RESEARCH CENTER FOR AN HISPANIC WOMEN'S CONFERENCE
    $17,900.00;$17,900.00
    United States; Fordham University
  - Fordham University (09301369), 1993 September 01-1995 May 31 (Reel 7084)
    PROJECT SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF NEW YORK CITY'S NEW HISPANIC POPULATIONS
    $107,000.00;$107,000.00
    McClymont, Mary (Mary E.);Romero, Anthony D.
    New York (N.Y.); Hispanic Americans -- New York (State); Fordham University
  - Fordham University (09601252), 1996 September 01-2000 June 30 (Reel 8776)
    SUPPORT FOR THE SOCIAL INDICATORS PROJECT AT THE FORDHAM INSTITUTE FOR INNOVATION IN SOCIAL POLICY
  - Fordham University (09601255), 1996 July 01-1997 June 30 (Reel 7299)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON THE INDUSTRIAL AREAS FOUNDATION COMMUNITY ORGANIZING MODEL
    Anglin, Roland;Smith, Marcia A.
  - Fordham University (09700345), 1997 January 01-2004 January 31 (Reel 9174)
    Support for a professional development program for practicing school superintendents
    $385,000.00;$385,000.00
    New York (N.Y.); New York (State); Fordham University
  - Fordham University (09800939), 1998 April 01-2002 March 31 (Reel 8880)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON STRATEGIES FOR BUILDING SOCIAL ASSETS AMONG DISADVANTAGED POPULATIONS IN THE UNITED STATES
    United States; Poor--Services for--United States--Congresses; Minorities--Services for--United States--Congresses; Economic development -- United States -- Congresses; Fordham University
  - Fordham University (09900299), 1999 January 01-2001 March 31 (Reel 9033)
    CONTINUED SUPPORT FOR THE SOCIAL INDICATORS PROJECT AT THE INSTITUTE FOR INNOVATION IN SOCIAL POLICY (0960-1252)
    United States; Social sciences--Study and teaching--United States; Fordham University
  - Fordham University (10051873), 2000 August 01-2001 December 31 (Reel 8918)
    RE-PRINT AND UPDATE A CLASSIC URBAN STUDY WE'RE STILL HERE: THE RISE, FALL, AND RESURRECTION OF THE SOUTH BRONX
    $33,500.00;$33,500.00